Rock, Eli Arbitration Files 5813
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Eli Rock Arbitration Files
1942-1974
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rock, Eli
5813
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Papers.
5710651
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 20, 2005
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3035: Eric Polisar Papers 5813: Eli Rock Arbitration Files 6004 OHT: NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Transcripts 6206: Clyde Summers Office Files 6338: David P. Miller Arbitration Papers
Arbitration, Industrial.; Industrial relations; Rock, Eli.; National Academy of Arbitrators
5710651
- Series I: National Academy of Arbitrators (Box 1)
  - Appointments - new committee members and new regional chairmen, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Arrangements Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
  - Atlanta Meeting - Annual., 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
    Scope and Contents
    includes minutes, address.
  - Board of Governor's and Membership Meeting., 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - Ethnics Committee., 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  - Executive Committee., 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
  - Newsletter., 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Overseas Correspondents, Committee on., 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Program Committee., 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 16-18)
  - Public Employment Disputes, Committee on., 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 19-21)
  - Regional Activities., 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 22-24)
  - Seidenberg Committee - Special Committee on National Railway Adjustment Board Matters., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Simkin Committee., 1965-1974 (Box 1, Folder 26-34)
    includes Code of Ethics, comments, etc.
- Series II: Public Employee Relations, 1953-1963 (Box 1)
  - AFSCME - New England Conference, Concord, MA., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Building Trades., 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    includes: Ordinance, Philadelphia Regulations Governing Labor Standards Complaint Procedure.
  - Cornell University Seminar - New York City., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    6/10/63. "Practical Labor Relations in the Public Sector."; Grievance Handling and Negotiation In the Governmental Agency.
  - Other Cities - Practices, Contracts, etc., 1955-1962 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Memorandum Report on the Personnel Provisions of the City Charter, Hartford, CT.; Agreement-City of New Haven and AFSCME, Local 713.
  - Philadelphia: City Hall - Board of Labor Standards., 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Philadelphia: City Hall - Labor Relations material., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Practical Labor Relations in the Public Service by Eli Rock"; Sub-Committee Report on Labor Relations in the Public Service in Pennsylvania - A Need for Investigation and Clarification" by Eli Rock & Jefferson B. Fordham.
  - Philadelphia: City Hall - Press Releases., 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 44-42)
  - Philadelphia Convention Hall., 1954-1961 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Philadelphia - Correspondence re Labor Relations., 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Philadelphia - Problems of Construction and Other Contract Jobs., 1953-1962 (Box 1, Folder 47-48)
  - Philadelphia - Problems of Construction and Other Contract Jobs. (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - "Problems and Potential and Public Service Collective Bargaining - The Philadelphia Story" by Eli Rock., 1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Public Employee Relations Research - Correspondence., 1942-1958 (Box 2, Folder 4-9)
  - Public Employee Relations Research., 1952-1960 (Box 2, Folder 10-20)
    Includes: "The Michigan Civil Service Hearing Board Report and Recommendations" by Charles C. Killingsworth & Kelvin J. Segal; "Cases Appealed to Michigan Civil Service Board" by Killingsworth & Segal; "Grievance Machinery For State Civil Service Employee
  - Public Personnel Association Speech, Providence, RI., 1957 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Eastern Region Conference, May, 1957. "Dynamics of a Sound Labor-Management Program Within Framework of the Civil Service."
  - "Salsburg, Sidney - Paper for the Fund For The Republic., 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 22-24)
    Corres., notes re implementation of the right of public employee to join unions.
  - Speech - South American. (Conference of Public Services Organizations of Western Hemisphere.), 1959 (Box 2, Folder 25-28)
    *A New Dimension in Civil Service* by Col. A.E. Garey & Marjorie S. Mueller; "The P.S.I. - What Is It and Why Organizations of Civil Servants and Public Employees Should Join It" by Paul Tofahrn; "Development and Progress of Trade Unions in Public Service
  - University of Pennsylvania Project. Labor Relations in Local Government Public Service., 1955-1963 (Box 2, Folder 29-41)
  - Miscellaneous., 1952-1961 (Box 2, Folder 42-44)
    Correspondence, etc.